https://www.atlantaballet.com/privacy-policy

Centre for Dance EducationSubscribeDonate
AboutPerformancesGroup SalesCalendarGet InvolvedSupport UsPrivacy PolicyAtlanta Ballet Privacy PolicyEffective Date: February 13, 2019 Lat Updated: February 25, 2019The Atlanta Ballet (“Atlanta Ballet,” “we”, “us” or “our”) Privacy Policy governs how we collect, use and disclose information about you obtained from users of our website and services. We may collect information about you in conjunction with providing products and services. This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information about you that we collect through our services (social media pages, email messages and direct communications with users) and Atlanta Ballet and Atlanta Ballet Centre for Dance Education websites.  By use of our services and websites and by providing your personal information to us, you acknowledge this Privacy Policy. If any term in this Privacy Policy is unacceptable to you, do not provide us your personal information or use atlantaballet.com, tickets.atlantaballet.com, centre.atlantaballet.com, or www.atlantaballet.networkforgood.com/projects/16087-friends-of-atlanta-ballet. Services are controlled and operated by us from the United States, and are not intended to subject us to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the United States. Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and by using the Services you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may have different data protection rules than those of your country. PERSONAL INFORMATION
Types of “Personal Information” That May be Collected:NamePostal addressTelephone numberEmail addressAtlanta Ballet account IDFacebook public profileTwitter handleInstagram handle and public
profileStandard Google Analytics tracking, custom events (engagements on site), and eCommerce data; PII is not collected and User ID tracking is not utilizedIf you submit any Personal Information relating to other people to us or to our service providers in connection with the products and services, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.How We Collect Personal InformationWe collect Personal Information that you provide while completing the following activities:Your purchases and donations made through the Atlanta Ballet websites; by phone with Atlanta Ballet Patron Services, employees, and authorized third party telemarketers; email with Atlanta Ballet Patron Services or employees; in-person at the Atlanta Ballet box office at 1695 Marietta Blvd NW, Atlanta, GA 30318; and by mail.Your purchase online, by phone, in-person, and by mail at the box offices of Ticketmaster, Cobb Energy Performing Arts Centre, Sandy Springs Performing Arts Center, Gwinnett Infinite Energy Theatre, the Fox Theatre, and other presenting venues.Your purchases and registrations for the Atlanta Ballet Centre for Dance Education made on centre.atlantaballet.com, by phone, fax, email, in-person with an employee of Atlanta Ballet, and by mail.Donations made on https://atlantaballet.networkforgood.com/projects/16087-friends-of-atlanta-ballet.Purchases and donations made on https://501auctions.com/balletball.Comments you post on atlantaballet.com and centre.atlantaballet.com.Google Analytics tracking of your visits to atlantaballet.com, tickets.atlantaballet.com, centre.atlantaballet.com, including engagements on site (custom events) and eCommerce tracking; data is collected using Google Tag Manager via DOM scraping and the DataLayer (eCommerce).Google Analytics tracking of your Atlanta Ballet purchase on foxtheatre.org.Your written correspondence sent via mail, email, and fax.Your likes, shares and comments on Atlanta Ballet and Atlanta Ballet Centre for Dance Education Twitter, Facebook, and Instagram posts and channels.Clicking, liking, commenting, sharing, or tagging friends on Atlanta Ballet and Atlanta Ballet Centre for Dance Education sponsored Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram ads.Clicking on Atlanta Ballet ads posted on third party sites directly or via Quantcast (digital advertising network) or Google Ads.Information
shared by you, on message boards, chat, profile pages and blogs and other
services to which you are able to post information and materials
(including, without limitation, our Social Media Pages). Please note that
any information you post or disclose through these services will become
public information, and may be available to users of the Services and to
the general public. We urge you to be very careful when deciding to
disclose your Personal Information, or any other information, on the
Services.We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive Personal Information (e.g., social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the Services or otherwise to us.Uses of Personal InformationTo respond to your inquiries and
fulfill your requests, such as sending eNewsletters, brochures, postcards,
updates, phone calls, and e-mails.To send administrative information
to you, for example, information regarding the products and services and
changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.To complete and fulfill your
purchase, for example, to process your payments, have your order delivered
to you, communicate with you regarding purchase and provide you with
related customer service.To send you marketing
communications that we believe may be of interest to you.To personalize your experience with
the services by presenting products, services, and offers tailored to you
via phone call, email, or print mailings, unless you have opted out of one
of these communication methods.To allow you to participate in
drawings of chance and similar promotions and to administer these
activities. Some of these activities have additional rules, which could
contain additional information about how we use and disclose your Personal
Information, so we suggest that you read these rules carefully.To facilitate social sharing
functionality.To allow you to send messages to a
friend through the Services. By using this functionality, you are telling
us that you are entitled to use and provide us with your friend’s name and
email addressFor campaign tracking with user/traffic reporting in Google Analytics and eCommerce data.For our business purposes, such as
data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new
products, enhancing, improving or modifying our Services, identifying
usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns
and operating and expanding our business activities. As we believe to be
necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside
your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to
respond to requests from public and government authorities including
public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d)
to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations; (f) to
protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of you or
others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the
damages that we may sustain.Please note that we keep contact information, including but not limited to name, phone number, email, and mailing address in our database in perpetuity. We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.Disclosure of Personal InformationWe also may disclose the Personal Information we collect about you as follows:To our third party service
providers who provide services such as data analysis, payment processing,
order fulfillment, information technology and related infrastructure
provision, customer service, email delivery, credit card processing,
auditing and other similar services.Traffic data (page views and clicks/events) and eCommerce data (revenue, order ID and quantity) to third party agencies for digital marketing/retargeting campaigns and campaign tracking.To third parties to permit them to
call you about services or special offers and send you printed marketing
communications, unless you have opted out of such sharing.To a third party in the event of
any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or
other disposition of all or any portion of our business, or assets
(including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).As we believe to be necessary or
appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country
of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests
from public and government authorities including public and government
authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms
and conditions; (e) to protect our operations; (f) to protect our rights,
privacy, safety or property, and/or that of you or others; and (g) to
allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may
sustain.Other Information We May CollectBrowser and device informationInformation collected through
cookies, pixel tags and other technologiesDemographic information and other
information provided by youAggregated informationThrough your browser or device:
Certain information is collected by most browsers or automatically through
your device, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, computer
type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, operating system name and
version, device manufacturer and model, language, Internet browser type
and version and the name and version of the Services you are using. We use
this information to ensure that the Services function properly.Using cookies: Cookies are pieces
of information stored directly on the computer that you are using. Cookies
allow us to collect information such as browser type, time spent on the
Services, pages visited, language preferences, and other anonymous traffic
data. We and our service providers use the information for security
purposes, to facilitate navigation, display information more effectively,
and to personalize your experience while using the Services, as well as
for online tracking purposes. We can recognize your computer to assist
your use of the Services. We also gather statistical information about the
usage of the Services in order to continually improve the design and
functionality, understand how the Services are used and to assist us with
resolving questions regarding the Services. Cookies further allow us to
select which of our advertisements or offers are most likely to appeal to
you and display them while you are on the Services. We may also use
cookies in online advertising to track responses to our advertisements and
we may use cookies or other files to track your use of other websites. If
you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, you can
decline cookies; however, if you do not accept these cookies, you may
experience some inconvenience in your use of the Services. For example,
you also may not receive advertising or other offers from us that are
relevant to your interests and needs.Using pixel tags and other similar
technologies: Pixel tags (also known as web beacons and clear GIFs) may be
used in connection with some Services to, among other things, track the
actions of users of the Services (including email recipients), measure the
success of our marketing campaigns and compile statistics about usage of
the Services and response rates.Using Adobe Flash technology and
other similar technologies: We may use Flash and or other technologies to,
among other things, collect and store information about your use of the
Services.IP Address: Your “IP Address” is a
number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using
by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). An IP Address may be identified
and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user accesses
the Services, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were
visited. Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice and is done
automatically by many websites. We use IP Addresses for purposes such as
calculating usage levels of the Services, helping diagnose server
problems, and administering the Services.From you: Information such as your
location, as well as other information, such as your preferred means of
communication, is collected when you voluntarily provide this information.
Unless combined with Personal Information, this information does not
personally identify you or any other user of the Services.By aggregating information:
Aggregated Personal Information does not personally identify you or any
other user of the Services, (for example, we may aggregate Personal
Information to calculate the percentage of our users who have a particular
telephone area code).Please note that we may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. If we are required to treat Other Information as Personal Information under applicable law, then we may use it as described in “Other Information we collect” section above, as well as for all the purposes for which we use and disclose Personal Information.In some instances, we may combine Other Information with Personal Information (such as combining your name with your geographical location). If we combine any Other Information with Personal Information, the combined information will be treated by us as Personal Information as long as it is combined.PRIVACY & THIRD PARTIESThis Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties, including any third party operating any site or service to which the Services link. The inclusion of a link on the Services does not imply our endorsement of the linked site or service.Please note that we are not responsible for the collection, usage and disclosure policies and practices (including the data security practices) of other organizations, such as Facebook, Apple, Google, Microsoft, RIM or any other app developer, app provider, social media platform provider, operating system provider, wireless service provider or device manufacturer, including any Personal Information you disclose to other organizations through or in connection with our Social Media Pages.We seek to use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information within our organization. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and it is the user’s responsibility to take measure to ensure all information and data is secure.USE BY MINORSOur Services are not intended for users under the age of 13 (a “minor”) and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from minors. If we become aware that a minor is using our Services, we will delete their information from our records. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage in order to verify that minors are not using our Services.We may change this Privacy Policy. Please take a look at the “Effective Date” legend at the top of this page to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Services. Your use of the Services following these changes means that you acknowledge the revised Privacy Policy.CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTSPlease refer to the above sections listing in detail the type of Personal Information collected and how it used for users living in California.CONTACT & OPTING OUTIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact:Atlanta Ballet
1695 Marietta Blvd NW
Atlanta, GA 30318Opting Out of the Collection of Personal InformationIf you no longer wish to receive marketing communications from Atlanta Ballet, please email patronservices@atlantaballet.com.If you no longer wish to receive marketing communications from Atlanta Ballet Centre for Dance Education, please email admissions@atlantaballet.com.You can opt out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features we use, through Ads Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or any other available means (for example, the NAI's consumer opt-out or at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).Atlanta Ballet Newsletter Sign Up* indicates required
Email Address
*
First Name
*
Last Name
I am interested in PerformancesBehind the Scenes Exclusives from Atlanta BalletClasses for ChildrenClasses for Adults
AboutPerformancesGroup SalesCalendarGet InvolvedSupport UsCentre For Dance EducationSubscribeDonatePressCalendarGet InvolvedPrivacy Policy
Atlanta Ballet
Gennadi Nedvigin | Artistic Director
Copyright © 2020 Atlanta Ballet. All Rights Reserved.
